[{"id":"wLYJqLdFz","serial":"1","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","oddipok":"whats your father name","question":"whats your father name","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas","answer":"option_d"},{"id":"1lS_Sdaod","serial":"1","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","oddipok":"whats your father name","question":"whats your father name","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas","answer":"option_d"},{"id":"nMUwMEskD","serial":"1","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","oddipok":"whats your father name","question":"whats your father name","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas","answer":"option_d"},{"id":"OhvARcaDh","serial":"1","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","oddipok":"whats your father name","question":"whats your father name","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas","answer":"option_d"},{"id":"A7lF65UpW","serial":"1","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","oddipok":"whats your father name","question":"whats your father name","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas","answer":"option_d"},{"id":"LB0CRke86","serial":"1","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","oddipok":"whats your father name","question":"whats your father name","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas","answer":"option_d"},{"id":"kIG2QHg40","serial":"1","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","oddipok":"whats your father name","question":"whats your father name","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas","answer":"option_d"},{"id":"x9-dEmK_f","serial":"1","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","oddipok":"whats your father name","question":"whats your father name","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas","answer":"option_d"},{"id":"9GtglPpzP","serial":"1","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","oddipok":"whats your father name","question":"whats your father name","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas","answer":"option_d"},{"id":"BrSO4mcPr","serial":"1","classes":"6","bookName":"Bangla_1st_paper","chapter":"2","type":"hard","oddipok":"whats your father name","question":"whats your father name","option_a":"korim","option_b":"salam","option_c":"borkot","option_d":"aklas","answer":"option_d"}]